Struggling with insomnia? Worried by anxiety?
正经受失眠和焦虑的困扰？
The first piece of advice that you are likely to see is to try breathing exercises.
你最可能看到的第一条建议就是尝试呼吸练习。
From ancient yoga practitioners to modern health professionals, experts have made this recommendation.
从古代的瑜伽修行者到现代的健康专业人士，专家们都提出了这个建议。
But how can simple breathing activities have such a significant effect on our mental and physical health?
但是，简单的呼吸活动怎能对我们的身心健康产生如此显著的影响呢？
Once we consider how essential oxygen is for life, it might seem obvious that focusing on this can help our health.
一旦我们考虑到氧气对生命有多么重要，事情就显而易见了––专注于呼吸有助于健康。
Our nervous system instinctively regulates the flow of oxygen into our lungs.
我们的神经系统本能地调节氧气进入肺部的流量。
Possibly because of body image concerns, many people hold in their stomachs, taking shallow breaths.
可能是因为担忧身体形象，许多人收腹，进行浅呼吸。
This can lead our body to increase our breathing rate to compensate.
这可能导致我们的身体通过增加呼吸频率来补偿。
Our breathing also gets faster when we're stressed or anxious.
当我们感到压力或焦虑时，呼吸也会变快。
When this happens, our sympathetic nervous system triggers a fight-or-flight response.
当这种情况发生时，我们的交感神经系统会触发战斗抑或逃跑的反应。
As well as affecting breathing, this increases our heart rate and produces adrenaline to prepare our muscles for action.
除了影响呼吸，这还会增加心率并产生肾上腺素，让肌肉做好行动准备。
Stress and anxiety can thus be linked with rapid breathing.
因此，压力和焦虑可能与快速呼吸相关。
To recover from a threat, our parasympathetic nervous system can put our body into a rest-and-digest state allowing us to relax and be calm.
为了从威胁中恢复正常状态，我们的副交感神经系统可以将身体置于休息和消化状态，让我们放松和平静。
In this state, breathing and heart rates slow.
在这种状态下，呼吸和心率会减慢。
However, it appears that slow, deep breathing can also make this happen.
然而，缓慢的深呼吸似乎也能实现这一点。
It's also notable that when we focus on breathing techniques, we can be distracted from the issues that are causing us stress.
同样值得注意的是，当我们专注于呼吸技巧时，我们可能将不再关注导致压力的问题。
Experts recommend using our diaphragm to inhale deeply, filling our lungs completely and then holding our breath for a few seconds before exhaling.
专家建议使用横膈膜来深吸气，完全充满肺部，然后在呼气前屏住呼吸几秒钟。
Other recommended techniques include breathing through alternating nostrils.
其他推荐的技巧包括通过交替鼻孔呼吸。
So next time you feel anxious or stressed, why not try some breathing techniques to help you relax?
所以，下次你感到焦虑或压力大时，为什么不试试一些呼吸技巧来帮助自己放松呢？